<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Paas]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Paas]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/eurion/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 16:33:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/eurion/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Platform as a Service (PaaS)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Platform as a Service (PaaS)</h1><p>Payments and transactional capabilities are no longer strictly the domain of a few, largely closed players. Today’s increasingly mobile and payments-focused environment requires faster deployment, greater interconnectivity among systems and strict compliance – and all under the right economics.
 
As a result, financial and non-financial institutions around the globe are increasingly turning to fintech companies – specialists with the experience, credentials and highly sophisticated tools to accelerate innovation. In addition, new cloud and license-based models are replacing the traditional owned, on-premise, CapEx intensive approach to technology.
 
NovoPayment’s Platform as a Service (PaaS) offering facilitates the creation of new products and services and the integration of third party systems via a bank-grade, highly scalable, and cost-effective model.
</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0895eb60736ea7b14be4c5d3a67591db4746a3c6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://travelaway.me/sleep-beneath-stars-italian-alps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">595e53f0-6541-4a7d-82a7-0929e1408c8f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 16:33:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Truly Tokyo Online Travel Guide]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Truly Tokyo Online Travel Guide</h1><p>Lonely Planet's Japan, Kyoto and Discover Japan guide author Chris Rowthorn, a longtime Kyoto resident who founded Inside Kyoto, has now tackled the city that plays muse to many all over the world: Tokyo. Truly Tokyo is a new online guide, entirely written by Rowthorn himself, that services first-timers and regular visitors.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3a537e3e634f758df36edc40db381ea53936da3d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/travel/truly-tokyo-online-travel-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">18f6131e-cf66-47ef-9946-e56f70774f84</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 16:26:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>